export const quiz = [
      {
        question: "Which one is the correct name for Rajma?",
        options1: "Brack Bohnen",
        options2: "Kidney Bohnen",
        options3: "Rosinen",
        options4: "Kali Dall",
        ans: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "What is the meaning of gehacht?",
        options1: "Chopped",
        options2: "Sabut",
        options3: "Black",
        options4: "Dose",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "How Much Quantity in one carton of Lamm Ohne Knochen?",
        options1: "5kg. block",
        options2: "2.27kg. block",
        options3: "10-12 kg",
        options4: "30 kg",
        ans: 3,
      },
      {
        question: "Alternate name of French Fries?",
        options1: "Pommas",
        options2: "Frulling Rolley",
        options3: "Wan-Tan",
        options4: "Ajino Moto",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "Which one is not a Rice?",
        options1: "Guard",
        options2: "Veetee",
        options3: "Punjabi gold",
        options4: "Spinat",
        ans: 4,
      },
      {
        question: "How many stange in MDH carton?",
        options1: "6",
        options2: "1",
        options3: "5",
        options4: "10",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "Which one is the name of Kalonji?",
        options1: "Nigela Seeds",
        options2: "Fennel Seeds",
        options3: "Star ani Seeds",
        options4: "Azwin Seeds",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "How many Dose of Pizza sauce in Mutti Brand?",
        options1: "3",
        options2: "6",
        options3: "12",
        options4: "8",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "Mainly use of Kapern?",
        options1: "For Pizza",
        options2: "For Sabji",
        options3: "For Packing",
        options4: "Tandoor item",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "Which one is not Pizza mehl?",
        options1: "Ziegenaus",
        options2: "Farina ",
        options3: "Cheetah atta ( Brown )",
        options4: "405 ",
        ans: 3,
      },
      {
        question: "Which one is correct answer for Pelati brands?",
        options1: "Mutti, Sacra, La rosino",
        options2: "Pilsbri, Farina, Ashirwad",
        options3: "Mutti, Cheetah, La perla",
        options4: "Sacra, Mutti, Frina",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "Which one is the thali wali packing?",
        options1: "R819",
        options2: "R1 ",
        options3: "R844",
        options4: "R879 ",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "â€¢	How many stuck in Punjabi samosa packing?",
        options1: "10 stuck",
        options2: "20 stuck ",
        options3: "50 stuck",
        options4: "10 to 12 stuck ",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "How many types of Shami kebab we have?",
        options1: "2",
        options2: "4 ",
        options3: "6",
        options4: "8",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "Kaiser gamuse is _____ Product.",
        options1: "Fresh sabji",
        options2: "Soupe Bruve ",
        options3: "Zhinga",
        options4: "Frozen Sbji ",
        ans: 4,
      },
      {
        question: "Biggest Zhinga we have?",
        options1: "8-12",
        options2: "6-8 ",
        options3: "O five",
        options4: "31-40 ",
        ans: 3,
      },
      {
        question: "Which one is available in 9 kg. block & 3 block in a carton?",
        options1: "Lasch fillet",
        options2: "See Lux fish ",
        options3: "Thunfish",
        options4: "Jandra filets ",
        ans: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Is that any packing of thali wali packing in Seagal schale?",
        options1: "Yes",
        options2: "NO",
        options3: "",
        options4: "",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "How many types of Becher schale in 50 ml?",
        options1: "2",
        options2: "1 ",
        options3: "4",
        options4: "5 ",
        ans: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Which one is family packing pizza carton?",
        options1: "26x26x4",
        options2: "40x40x4 ",
        options3: "60x40x5",
        options4: "49x33x4 ",
        ans: 4,
      },
      {
        question: "How many stuck in Brot edamer kase 40% packing?",
        options1: "12",
        options2: "15 ",
        options3: "4",
        options4: "3",
        ans: 3,
      },
      {
        question: "How many pcs of Butter tikki in a carton?",
        options1: "250 gm x 40 pc.",
        options2: "200 gm x 40 pc.",
        options3: "2 kg. x 4 stuck",
        options4: "12 pcs",
        ans: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "Which one is Beer Brand we have?",
        options1: "Sula",
        options2: "Pinogricho ",
        options3: "Marlot",
        options4: "Helles",
        ans: 4,
      },
      {
        question: "How Much quantity in Rasanand Alfanso Mango pulp?",
        options1: "20 kg.",
        options2: "850 gm. ",
        options3: "3.2 kg.",
        options4: "240 gm.",
        ans: 3,
      },


];
